youqueen.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy - YouQueen

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which YOUQUEEN LIMITED's YouQueen.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.youqueen.com](http://www.youqueen.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by YOUQUEEN LIMITED.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## What is a “Cookie”?

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## How we use collected information

YOUQUEEN LIMITED may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  *  _To improve customer service_  Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  *  _To improve our Site  _We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Advertising & Affiliate Disclosure

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

YouQueen.com may receive financial compensation for certain advertisements displayed on our Site or link recommendations we make.

Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Changes to this privacy policy

YOUQUEEN LIMITED has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Copyright

This website and its content is copyright of YouQueen.com – © YouQueen LLC 2015. All rights reserved.

Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:

  * you may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only
  * you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material.

You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.

## Disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by YouQueen.com and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of YouQueen.com

We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, YouQueen.com takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

## Terms of Service

If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern YouQueen.com’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.

The term ‘YouQueen.com’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is YouQueen Limited, Geneva Place, Waterfront Drive, PO Box 3469, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * This website uses cookies to monitor browsing preferences. If you do allow cookies to be used, the following personal information may be stored by us for use by third parties: Google Analytics.
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s). ** **

YouQueen LTD collects some personal information from our visitors via pop ups and landing pages, such as email address and name. We do this to better personalize our communication and marketing messages. By submitting my information, you acknowledge that you will be receiving educational and promotional emails from YouQueen LTD. You also have the option of unsubscribing anytime by clicking the Unsubscribe button at the bottom of every email, and YouQueen LTD will delete your information completely from our systems. YouQueen LTD will not share your information with third-parties and that your information will be safely and securely stored within an email service provider YouQueen LTD uses. If there are any changes to this agreement, YouQueen LTD must first inform you and ask you for your consent.  If you have any questions at all you can contact us by sending an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2a4945445e4b495e6a53455f5b5f4f4f4404494547) and we’ll get back to you as soon as we can.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

YouQueen Limited  
Geneva Place  
Waterfront Drive  
PO Box 3469, Road Town  
Tortola  
British Virgin Islands  
Or reach us at: +1 917 310 3210

This document was last updated on 23 June 2015
